Word just came in.
Train is still delayed.
I'm done waiting.
Let's go find this fucking bunker.
Something you're not
telling me. Gary.
I'd pick sooner
rather than later to fess up.
All this time.
Teri's been trying to find a way there.
She doesn't need
another barrel of biofuel.
She can just get on that train.
There's five guys
patrolling with M16s.
I'm gonna create a distraction
so I can go in and get Teri.
Cal.
I was in love with him.
We can get a divorce. and you and I can
do all that romantic shit together.
We can hold hands in public
and talk about our love languages.
All of it.
I want all of it with you.
You're Cal Bradford's son.
You're the guy who helped
my dad build all this.
I designed it all.
- God forgive me.
- Good.
'Cause you're gonna help me
blow the fucking doors open.
- Please help me.
- Samantha.
You will be richer
than your wildest dreams.
You won't need
a single other client.
Good luck. kiddo.
- And how is Alex?
- Alex is well.
The power problem has been resolved?
Oh. yes. I've made sure of that.
What do you remember
about what happened?
Not much. really.
What the fuck did you do?!
He was gonna
blow your brains out.
But you're no use to me
if you're dead.
This is Agent Driscoll.
Hercules is down.
It was Agent Robinson.
Oh. my God.
there's so much blood!
Breathe. Breathe.
Are you sure nobody's
coming for you. love?
Get her out!
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I know. I know.
Yes. It's okay.
It's okay.
Hang in there.
The first few days are always tough.
I'm just happy
she finally stopped crying.
Aw. yeah. I hear you.
She's a very cute baby.
Little girl. yes?
W-When was she born?
Just the other day?
Mm-hmm.
Was the baby born on June 6th
at 12:01 a.m.?
The girl?
- What?
- Sir. please.
It's her. isn't it?
Holy shit. it's her.
- Listen to me. She's a killer.
- Security!
Not now. but she will be.
- But she can be stopped.
- Sir.
- Oh. no. no. no. no. no. no.
- She can be stopped
- when it matters.
- Security!
I have a message for that baby.
I have a message for that little girl.
She can be stopped
when it matters.
You need to listen to me!
- I have a message for that baby.
- Get back!
I have a message
for that little girl.
- You gotta go now!
- She can be stopped when it matters!
- I have a message for that baby!
- Jane. Jane. stop crying.
Jane.
Stop crying. Jane!
I'm gonna set the explosive
near those yellow barricades
and come back here.
Then. I'm gonna detonate the bomb.
When the bomb attracts attention.
I'm gonna go in and get Teri.
- Any questions?
- Nope.
Uh. wait. just one.
Uh. what am I doing?
- Nothing.
- Got it. consider it done.
Why does the explosive
need to be in that spot?
The guards won't leave
their post if the explosion
isn't close enough
to cause a threat for them.
Too far away and it won't be.
That spot's our mark
because it's a safe distance away
and no one will get hurt.
but it still poses a threat.
Any other questions?
Yeah. actually.
How the hell
are you gonna pull this off?
Our little boy.
he had a train phase.
Loved 'em.
There was a two-year span
where all presents
for birthdays or Christmas.
they had to be trains.
Tracks. cabooses.
dining cars. the works.
And I would set up
these elaborate train tracks for him.
And all he wanted to do
was smash the trains into each other.
Smash. smash. smash.
Used to drive me fucking nuts.
Why couldn't he just let the trains
ride along their tracks?
But maybe the kid
was onto something.
Maybe it's not fun to play with trains
that ride smoothly along their tracks.
Maybe the thing
that's interesting about trains
is the possibility that
these huge metal contraptions
could one day
crash into one another.
How am I gonna pull this off?
I'm gonna run my ass down there.
break a few necks
if anyone gets in my way.
and I'm gonna get
my fucking wife back.
Watch my back
and don't touch anything.
I'm here to pick up Sinatra.
- On whose orders?
- Mine.
Baines is gone
and she's back in charge.
Fuck with me and find out.
I don't need it.
Thank you. sweetheart.
- Good morning.
- Jane.
Help me with my jacket?
Yes. of course.
The group outside
the bunker walls has grown.
They appear heavily armed.
Morton was able to secure footage
from the south mountainside
for this morning.
I was thinking that I could take
the long way to the meeting
so that you can
show up a little late.
You know. more of a power move.
Smart...
Good thinking. Jane.
Are you okay?
Are you sure you wanna go back
to work so quickly?
I'm fine. don't worry.
Mm.
- I love you.
Pinky up.
Climby. stop.
You're gonna make me
laugh and spill.
Jane. you're too old
to be talking to imaginary friends.
Dinner's ready.
and I'm not gonna reheat it.
Downstairs... Now.
Okay. now you've won $800 so far.
Come on.
it's gonna be so hot in there.
It's gonna be hot
and it's gonna be good.
You're gonna really enjoy it.
You know. Okay.
- Go 'head. you first.
- Get over here.
No. Climby.
Mom won't like that.
Okay. fine. I'll do it.
You don't have to yell.
Hey!
She locked us in.
No. Let us out. Jane.
- Hey. open up.
- Let us out.
It's not funny.
Jane. let us out right now!
Let us out right now.
or you are in big trouble!
I swear to God.
you're in big trouble.
That's it.
Unlock the door. Jane.
Unlock the door.
- Okay. get back here.
- Wait. I'm sorry. It was Climby!
- No.
- Climby told me to do it!
- Climby. Climby told me to do it.
- Enough.
Let me out.
That lunatic in the parking lot
was right about you.
You're the worst goddamn thing
that ever happened to me.
- Hey. Jane?
- Yeah?
Make sure nothing bad
happens to my mom. okay?
I... I won't let anything
happen to her.
You know that. right?
I promise.
I will never let anything happen.
- I'm telling you it's Alec.
- No. no. I'm...
- It's Alec.
- I'm pretty sure it's Alex.
- Pretty sure you're wrong.
- It's Alex Trebek.
I watched Jeopardy! every night
- since I was 14 years old.
- Were you watching
- with the sound off?
- I know for a fact it is Alec.
- Hold on a second. Hold on.
- It's Alec!
Hold on. I'm gonna look it up.
- I'm right.
- No.
- Suck it. baby.
- What?
- Suck it.
- No.
- I'm right. Yes.
- Give it to me.
During their playdate.
Elise's mom. Alex.
kept droning on and on. I...
I've done something terrible.
I crossed a line
no person should cross.
but Alex is our o-only chance. and...
Oh. I'm...
I'm not following.
I'm afraid of the person
I'm becoming. Gabi.
I'm afraid of the person I'm going
to have to be in order to save them.
Save who. Samantha?
I have to go.
You've got to be kidding me.
Garcia made pizza for breakfast.
Nice. James.
How 'bout a doggie bag for school?
Um. no. thanks.
I made our lunches last night.
Like I've been doing
for the past three years.
We don't need babysitters.
What we need for you to do
is your fucking jobs.
I heard that.
Good.
Because how can you guys just be
sitting here like nothing is happening?
People are disappearing.
my boyfriend was just arrested.
and you're sitting here
making pizza for breakfast.
To be fair. it is a breakfast pizza...
Why aren't you guys out there
fighting back?
Oh. I know.
It's because you rely on my dad
and Robinson to do literally everything
for you. just like always.
We were told to keep you guys safe
- and wait for them to return.
- Whatever.
Just make sure James
makes it to school and back.
I've got shit to do.
Hello. everyone.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
I'm sure you've all heard
about President Baines by now.
The suspect has been apprehended
and is currently in custody.
Agent Driscoll will provide us
with an official update.
Special Agent Robinson was detained
and is currently in custody.
She was a known associate
of Xavier Collins.
and her actions appear
to be a continuation
of the failed coup
she led with him.
Thank you. Agent Driscoll.
This is insane.
Two dead presidents now.
Murdered.
What are we gonna tell everyone?
They won't have time
to worry about Baines.
They're not gonna have time
to worry about another dead president?
No. We have bigger problems.
- What's going on?
- What is that?
A militia has amassed
outside our bunker doors.
People are alive out there?
We have no idea
what state they're in.
We have no idea what they want.
Over the past 48 hours.
the group has doubled in size.
They appear heavily armed
and quite serious.
They want to talk.
Now. I have a plan.
But I can't act on that plan
without the consent
of everyone at this table.
I won't do that again.
This is not a dictatorship.
We are a team.
It needs to be unanimous.
I think we should do it.
- Yes.
- Yes. yes. of course.
I'm on board.
Alright.
Here's what I propose.
It's nighttime 24/7 down here.
How do we really know
it's time for breakfast. huh?
How do we really know it's morning?
I'm tripping out.
They're lying to us. bro.
Find a seat.
It's cooked. dude.
He wants nothing to do with us
and he's weird as fuck.
We can't do this without him.
Have you thought about what I asked?
They always come back
to haunt us.
- I'm s... What?
- Our original sins.
Mine are down here.
It's quite poetic. actually.
- that I ended up here.
- Okay. s-sorry.
Are you gonna help us
get out of here or not?
But I guess it's what I deserve. right?
Jesus Christ.
Okay. um...
Yeah. thank you for nothing.
Loved you in Inglourious Basterds.
by the way.
You can't just bust open
the doors of this place.
It's a fortress.
Sit down.
In the emergency control room
on the systems level.
if the oxygen supply is shut off.
all the doors automatically open.
All of them.
for everyone in Paradise.
That's. that's it?
Well. how-how-how-how do we get to it?
Look to your right.
- You see a manhole?
- Yeah.
Those lead to a maintenance tunnel.
From there. it's pretty much
a straight shot. okay?
Well. it's welded shut.
Bit out in the open. don't you think?
There's one more of those down here
that they didn't weld shut.
I know exactly where it is.
You asked to see me?
Come sit.
I need to talk to you
about something.
Sit. Jane. please.
You made it their decision
to give you back power.
It was incredibly impressive.
Mrs. Redmond.
Sam is fine.
Thank you. Sam.
I find myself
in an interesting moment.
I'm gonna be honest. Jane.
you terrify me.
But my two closest
security team members are dead.
half of the Secret Service
was just in open revolt. and you...
you're what I've got.
You're the only person left down here
who knows my secrets.
But before we take the next step
in our relationship.
I have to know something.
After you shot me. you told me
that I was no use to you dead.
What did you mean?
I thought you didn't remember.
Things came back.
Well. I'm...
What I meant was...
I'm a killer.
It's what I've always been.
A weapon.
People I respect aim me
and I execute for them.
To serve my purpose.
I need someone like you.
You're no good to me
if you're dead.
I'm going to meet with them.
the militia...
and I need you to go out
and negotiate the terms.
- Outside?
- Yes.
Just you.
Let's try this again. Tell me who you are.
I told you.
I'm studying International Relations
at St. Petersburg University.
I live in Vaska with my three cats.
I'm just a regular girl who loves cats.
But you are still. by far.
the biggest pussy I've ever met.
Enough!
I know you're American.
Tell me who you work for.
Special Skills
Officer Driscoll. my office. please.
You didn't have
to let him off the hook.
I had him.
Jane... how are you enjoying
your time here at The Farm?
Well. I'm ready to get out
in the field.
Yeah. well. your intelligence scores
are off the charts.
Um. your psych eval is...
I had a hard childhood.
Something happened
when I was a baby
that really framed the way
my mom treated me.
- Sometimes I hear voices.
- I don't wanna know.
Never give them an excuse
to keep you down.
Look. Jane.
You're what. 105 pounds?
Radner is a misogynistic prick.
But when he's a foreign enemy
and has twice the anger Radner has.
you're done for.
You need to fight smarter.
Sit down.
Are you familiar
with the Stargate Project?
- No.
- It was a CIA-funded initiative
during the 1980s
that investigated the potential
of non-traditional techniques
for intelligence gathering.
The official program
at The Farm was terminated.
but the techniques were not.
Meditation is one of them.
Quieting the noise.
Quieting the voices inside your head.
A mentor taught me.
and I'd like to teach you. Jane.
I think the techniques could help.
- Would you like to give it a try?
- Sure.
'Kay.
So first. we're just gonna take
a deep breath in.
Feeling your ribcage expand.
And when you get to the top
of your breath. just hold.
And let go.
And feel the breath expand
into both hands.
Once you've mastered it.
you'll reach a point
where you'll feel like your mind
is floating outside your body.
You'll learn to think clearly
in impossible situations.
You will notice things
you didn't before:
mannerisms. patterns. behaviors.
Tell me who you work for.
That slap was the closest thing
you'll ever get
to a woman's touch.
you pencil-dicked incel.
Gah!
Open the doors.
It was like he was trying
to get himself arrested.
- It just doesn't make any sense.
- I'm sorry. girl.
Feels like it's just
one thing after another.
I need answers.
Ding. ding. ding.
Hi. Presley. right?
We haven't really talked.
My boyfriend's missing.
my father is God knows where
being blamed for everything.
And now. the closest person
I have left down here
got arrested
for something she didn't do.
What do you have to say
about all of that?
I literally have no idea
what you're talking about.
Look. I got a lot going on.
but this place
isn't what you think it is.
And your mother
isn't who you think she is.
Start there.
I know you didn't do it.
Hot Sherlock Holmes
in the house.
This place is crumbling.
And I'm convinced that it has something
to do with someone named Alex.
Sinatra. she...
You're a little too late. Doc.
And honestly. I have reached my limit
talking about your girl.
Okay. Alright. fair.
Did Cal ever say anything
about an Alex?
He hated Alex Rodriguez.
He was strangely intolerant
to major leaguers
that do performance-enhancing drugs.
but in all fairness.
the Yankees do suck.
Okay. we have to stop her.
Actually. Doc. I ain't gotta do shit
but stay Black and die.
You do realize that stopping Sinatra
might be the only way to clear your name?
Do you hear yourself right now?
Wake up.
She is undefeated
and will remain undefeated
because that is how
the system works.
They're gonna frame me
just like they framed X.
And you know what
I'm gonna do about it?
Jack-fucking-shit.
I'm gonna sit on my ass down here
and mourn the loss of my people.
and then wash my hands of all of it.
So. yeah. good luck with that.
Brooks. I'm ready
for my sponge bath.
Not yet. Brooks.
I'm not leaving without answers.
Sinatra is not the dangerous one.
What do you mean?
Sinatra remains untouchable
because of the people behind her.
It's the girl. Doc.
Jane.
I missed it.
X missed it.
But she is behind all of it:
Baines. Billy.
That girl. she is like nothing
I've ever seen before.
Gentlemen.
Head's up. head's up.
Oh!
Don't worry. it's just me.
The leader of our community
is willing to meet with you.
I've been asked
to deliver the terms.
Whoa!
Where's the cutie
with the cards?
I'm not fucking playing.
Where is he?
I'm here.
Whoa. Super cute.
Please. lower your gun.
My boss is willing to meet.
but only with you.
Understood. and fine.
but I'll be bringing my men.
You can bring two men. unarmed.
Ten. armed.
Two. no weapons.
Five. armed.
Five. no weapons.
You guys have apple pie in there?
- What?
- Apple pie.
Of all the things I crave.
and there's a lot.
good old-fashioned apple pie
is the thing that I think about the most.
Yeah. We have pie.
It's really good. actually.
Five men. unarmed...
and a slice of apple pie.
I'll see what I can do.
I'm gonna let him go
and head back now.
I would not recommend
moving on me.
I slowed it all down
and I saw it.
When he gets mad.
he leaves himself wide open.
I mean. I totally had him.
It was incredible.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
I got him with his own gun
in. like. 22 seconds.
Is everything okay?
Hm. I...
found out you-know-who
got the promotion I was up for.
You know he didn't even apply
until he found out
I was gunning for it?
Radner's in paramilitary operations.
That has nothing to do
with what you do.
And he's a child.
How?
He has a dick. Jane.
You're so much better
at your job than him.
No. seriously. you teach.
You actually want
your students to succeed.
Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
Why did you help me?
I mean. aside from
all the girl power shit.
There are other women
in the program.
Why me?
Because I think
you're incredibly special. Jane.
And I'm incredibly sad
that no one has ever told you.
What are those?
Oh! Controllers for the Wii.
You wanna play?
They agreed to the terms.
Okay. good.
Really great work. Jane.
- Thank you.
- I have something for you.
I tried to find the one you like.
but I think this is the newer version.
It's a Nintendo Switch.
Mom?
- Hi. sweetheart.
- I'll give you two a moment.
Your mom is the best.
Like. the best.
Yeah. Yeah. she is.
That's cool we both see it. you know?
Okay.
I need to know something.
and it can't wait.
Okay. what is it?
Talk to me.
Are you Sinatra?
"Sinatra" is just a code name
for the Secret Service.
- We've been over this.
- Well. then why was it written in the sky?
And what about those people
who are disappearing?
Some of those kids
are in my class. Mom.
I'm sorry this is happening.
I really am.
And I'm working on it. Hadley.
I promise. I had nothing to do
with putting them down there.
And I'm gonna get to the bottom of it
as soon as I'm able. okay?
- It should be just...
- Oh. Shit.
What up. Shawshank?
I see you're as obvious as ever.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You gonna try to get out
of one of these?
Make your big escape?
Yes. We're going to escape
through it tonight
while everyone's asleep.
Don't be a snitch.
- A snitch?
- Yeah.
That's cute.
You're gonna get yourselves killed.
- You know. if your dad could see...
- No. no. no.
No. no. no.
I-I do not need a lecture
from one of my father's
side pieces. okay?
- One of his side pieces?
- Yeah.
You know what?
My conscience is clear.
You're on your own.
Andy Dufresne.
Hi. Sorry to show up like this.
Look. I know you got the promotion
Officer Thomas was up for.
And I think it would mean a lot
to see a woman in that position.
- Oh.
- She really deserves it.
And I just wanted to let you know
in the hopes that you would
consider stepping down.
Well. thank you. Officer Driscoll.
That's. that's a really good point.
You know what else
is a really good point?
You getting the flying fuck
off my porch.
Jane. what are you doing here?
Sunday night dinner. no?
Oh. yes.
Um. I'm sorry. I just...
I'm. I'm a little... shook up.
Did you hear about Radner?
He was. he was attacked.
He's been in surgery for hours.
So. does that mean
you'll get the promotion?
What's in the bag. Jane?
You said Officer Radner
only got the promotion
because he had a dick.
Well. that's not an issue anymore.
Really great work. Jane.
You have more to offer the world
than what you've been told.
I'm proud of you. Jane.
She went home for the evening.
I'm not here for her.
I'm here for you.
For me?
I know what you did...
to Baines. Robinson.
To Pace.
If you know what I did...
then you know what I'm capable of.
You know. I did her bidding
myself for a while.
It doesn't end well.
It's different with us.
I don't think you're understanding me.
She's up to something.
And I'm gonna figure out what it is.
I'm coming for her.
If you come for her...
you come through me.
Shit.
- Hey. what's up?
- I'm sorry. Brooks.
For what?
Hey! The fuck you guys doing?
- Uh...
- Hey!
I wasn't a fucking side piece.
and I'll be damned
if I let his kid get pummeled.
Come on. In.
Uh. a-after you.
Help me with this?
I told you to stand watch.
What's the rest of my path
look like from up there?
Oh. um. I'm sorry.
There's an armed guard
on top of the tanker
facing three o'clock.
but that could change.
How 'bout this? This good?
That's good. just give me a sec!
If anything happens to me...
I want you to find her.
And tell her our kids
are in Colorado.
and that I came
all the way here to find her.
And that I made it.
And you make sure
that she's safe. okay?
You make sure
that she's taken care of.
That's all I ever wanted to do.
I'm sorry. Xavier.
Over here!
Watch out! There could be more!
Xavier?